<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="107">

    <author>Oscar Mods</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>True Reg Plate Manual</en>
		<de>Originales Kennzeichen Manuell</de>
		<fr>Véritable Plaque d'Immatriculation Manuelle</fr>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en>
            Adds a realistic manual plate transfer mechanic to Farming Simulator 25.

            Every tractor and vehicle keeps its own registration. By default all
            vehicles can share the same plate number, which is not realistic.
            This mod fixes that by requiring the player to physically transfer
            the plate from the tractor to the trailer by hand.

            HOW IT WORKS:
            1. Attach a trailer to your tractor.
            2. Exit the cab and walk to the rear of the tractor.
            3. When the prompt appears, press the interact key to take the plate.
               The registration will appear in your hand.
            4. Walk to the rear of the trailer.
            5. Press the interact key to attach the plate to the trailer.
               The trailer now permanently displays the tractor's registration.

            The plate stays on the trailer when you detach it. If you later
            attach that trailer to a different tractor, the old plate remains
            until you physically walk up and remove it, then fit the new one.

            To remove a plate walk to the rear of the trailer without carrying
            a plate and press the interact key when prompted.

            Multiplayer supported. Saves and loads correctly.
        </en>
		<de>
			Fügt Farming Simulator 25 einen realistischen manuellen
			Kennzeichen-Übertragungsmechanismus hinzu.

			Jeder Traktor und jedes Fahrzeug behält sein eigenes Kennzeichen.
			Standardmäßig können alle Fahrzeuge dieselbe Kennzeichennummer
			teilen, was nicht der Realität entspricht. Dieser Mod behebt das,
			indem der Spieler das Kennzeichen vom Traktor auf den Anhänger
			persönlich übertragen muss.

			SO FUNKTIONIERT ES:
			1. Hängen Sie einen Anhänger an Ihren Traktor.
			2. Verlassen Sie die Kabine und gehen Sie zum Heck des Traktors.
			3. Wenn die Eingabeaufforderung erscheint, drücken Sie die
			   Interaktionstaste, um das Kennzeichen zu nehmen. Das Kennzeichen
			   erscheint in Ihrer Hand.
			4. Gehen Sie zum Heck des Anhängers.
			5. Drücken Sie die Interaktionstaste, um das Kennzeichen am Anhänger
			   zu befestigen. Der Anhänger zeigt nun dauerhaft das Kennzeichen
			   des Traktors an.

			Das Kennzeichen bleibt am Anhänger, wenn Sie ihn abkoppeln. Wenn Sie
			den Anhänger später an einen anderen Traktor ankoppeln, bleibt das
			alte Kennzeichen, bis Sie es physisch abnehmen und das neue anbringen.

			Um ein Kennzeichen zu entfernen, gehen Sie ohne ein Kennzeichen in
			der Hand zum Heck des Anhängers und drücken Sie die Interaktionstaste,
			wenn Sie dazu aufgefordert werden.

			Multiplayer wird unterstützt. Speichern und Laden funktionieren korrekt.
		</de>
		<fr>
			Ajoute un mécanisme réaliste de transfert manuel de plaque
			d'immatriculation à Farming Simulator 25.

			Chaque tracteur et véhicule conserve sa propre immatriculation. Par
			défaut, tous les véhicules peuvent partager le même numéro de plaque,
			ce qui n'est pas réaliste. Ce mod y remédie en demandant au joueur de
			transférer physiquement la plaque du tracteur vers la remorque à la main.

			COMMENT ÇA MARCHE :
			1. Attachez une remorque à votre tracteur.
			2. Sortez de la cabine et marchez vers l'arrière du tracteur.
			3. Lorsque l'invite apparaît, appuyez sur la touche d'interaction pour
			   prendre la plaque. L'immatriculation apparaîtra dans votre main.
			4. Marchez vers l'arrière de la remorque.
			5. Appuyez sur la touche d'interaction pour fixer la plaque sur la
			   remorque. La remorque affiche désormais en permanence
			   l'immatriculation du tracteur.

			La plaque reste sur la remorque lorsque vous la détachez. Si vous
			attachez ensuite cette remorque à un autre tracteur, l'ancienne plaque
			reste en place jusqu'à ce que vous la retiriez physiquement et posiez
			la nouvelle.

			Pour retirer une plaque, approchez-vous de l'arrière de la remorque
			sans plaque en main et appuyez sur la touche d'interaction lorsque
			vous y êtes invité.

			Multijoueur pris en charge. La sauvegarde et le chargement
			fonctionnent correctement.
		</fr>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>store_trueRegPlate.dds</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <!--
        extraSourceFiles are loaded after the base game scripts but before any
        map or vehicle XML is processed, so our function wrappers on
        Attachable.postAttach / Attachable.postDetach are in place before any
        vehicle is spawned or loaded from a savegame.
    -->
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="TrailerPlateSyncManual.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="PlateHandoverManual.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

</modDesc>
